

52, 11th Main, 30th Cross Banashankari 2nd Stage Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

Skill

- ઢ varungupta3009

Experience



Corporate Operations Engineer II

Google

May 2023 - Present (2 mos)

Corporate Operations Engineer

Jan 2022 - May 2023 (1 yr 5 mos)

IT Resident

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 (6 mos)

Data and Reporting Analyst Hewlett Packard Enterprise Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 (7 mos)



Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 – Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

Education



PES University

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

K-PUC (CS), Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 – 2015

Publications & Awards

Twitter Spam Review Detection Using Hybrid Machine Learning Techniques Springer, November 2021, ISBN: 978-981-16-3690-5

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

Languages

हिंदी (Hindi) English ಕನ್ನಡ (Kannada) **Hobbies**

Reading

Gaming	
--------	--

Mu	sic

Knowledge and Skills

Python 3 Experience Skill	
JavaScript Experience Skill	
C/C++ Experience Skill	
Windows 7/ Experience	8/10

Frontend Design and Development

Experience	
Experience	
Skill	
ווואכ	

Full-Stack Web Development

Experience	
Skill	

Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)

Experience	
CI/III	

WordPress, CMS

Experience	
Skill	

Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Experience	
Experience	
Skill	
JKIII	

Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro

Experience	
Skill	
51(11)	

Blender, Pixar Renderman

Experience	
Skill	

Cloud Architechture (GCP)

Experience	
Experience	
Skill	
31(11)	

Generated	resume.\	VRG.rocks

About me

I am an experienced developer with proficiency in web design. Fluent in many computing languages with over 11 years of experience in Python, C++, and JS. Polymath, geek, and love to explore the bleeding edge of technology and internet. I am also a hobbyist designer and hacker.

Let's Connect

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

